happynews.com 2013-09-22

# Happy News - Real News. Compelling Stories. Always Positive.

**Updated as of November 24, 2008**

HappyNews is a property of Demand Media, Inc. (“HappyNews” or “we” or “us”).  HappyNews is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all our users. This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) applies to the personally identifying information (“PII”) collected online through HappyNews's Web site (the “Site”), which includes all of the HappyNews.com articles and videos and other services we provide on the Site (the “Service”). Please read the complete Policy below and contact us if you have any questions.  This Policy is part of and incorporated into the Terms of Use of the Site [http://happynews.com/termsofuse.aspx].  

  1. How Does HappyNews Collect Information?

_Type of Information We Collect._   We collect any information you enter on the Service or give us in any other way (such as through an email, survey, or letter). The information that we collect varies depending upon how you use our Service.  Our account registration process requires that you provide us with your user name, birthday and email address, and that you create and provide us with a password.  We may also request other information, such as but not limited to, your actual first and last name, gender, and zip code.   
_Information in Public Areas of the Site_.  Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily provide information in public areas of the Service, such as the user profile pages or forums, that information can be viewed and possibly used by others.  We therefore advise visitors not to disclose contact information, including phone number, email address, street address or instant messenger address (within these public areas) that they do not wish to share.  We are not responsible for PII you choose to submit in these public areas.  Also, we may highlight content you post to the public areas of the Service such as reviews or comments, such as by featuring your content on the Site’s home page.    
_Minors_.  We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register.  If you are under 13, do not attempt to register for our Site or send any information about yourself to us.  We recommend that prospective users between the ages of 13 and 17 ask their parents or other legal guardians for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.   
_Cookies_.  Like many websites, we use “cookies.”  Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser.  We use persistent, identifying cookies to remember your information and to link your activities to you.  While you can take steps to warn off, block or disable cookies, if you do, the Service may not function and appear as we have designed it.  Nonetheless, if you want to take these steps, you can do so by following the instructions associated with your browser.  Our cookies do not collect PII that you provide to us during the registration process, but they do collect other information such as the following:

  * the domain name and host from which you access the Internet and the Internet address of the site from which you direct-linked to ours;
  * the date and time you access the Site and pages you visit;
  * your computer's IP address and information about its operating system, platform and the Web browser type and version you use;
  * demographic and other non-personally identifiable profile information about you; and
  * information to combat fraud or misuse.

_Pixel Tags_.  In our emails to you, we may use “pixel tags” to determine if your email software or service can display html-formatted email (this helps us optimize the size of our email messages and conserve bandwith).  
_Collection of Information by Third Parties_.  Our Site may include third-party advertising, links to other websites, and other content from third party businesses. The content posted by these parties will be reasonably identifiable as coming from a third party.  We do not provide any PII to these advertisers, third-party websites, or other businesses, although on occasion we may mutually share non-personally identifiable (e.g., demographic) information to facilitate delivery of relevant advertisements.  These third-party websites, businesses, and advertisers, or advertising companies working on their behalf, sometimes use technology to deliver (or "serve") the advertisements that appear on our Site directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use cookies, JavaScript, web beacons (also known as action tags or single-pixel gifs), and other technologies to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize or optimize advertising content. We do not have access to or control over cookies or other technologies that they may use, and the information practices of these advertisers and third-party websites or businesses are not covered by this Policy but are covered by their respective privacy policies. Some, but not all, third party advertising companies provide a mechanism to opt-out of their technology.  For more information and an identification of advertisers that provide an opt-out mechanism, please click the following: http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.       
_Promotions, Sweepstakes, and Contests_.  From time to time, we may host a promotion, sweepstake, or contest on the Service.  You may be asked to provide personal information or permit the transfer to a third party of your personal information in connection with such promotion, sweepstake or contest.  It will be disclosed at the point of collection or transfer who is collecting or transferring the information and whose privacy statement applies, and it will be your choice whether or not you wish to permit such transfer or collection of personal information to a third party.

  2. What Does HappyNews Do With Collected Information? 

_Use of PII_.  We use your PII for purposes such as responding to your requests, monitoring and providing the Service, maintaining your account, providing you with advertising and non-advertising content that we believe would be of interest to you, enforcing our rights and the rights of third parties, and investigating and ensuring compliance with the Terms [http://happynews.com/termsofuse.aspx].  We also may use your PII to contact you regarding your account, such as to inform you that you have received an email from another member, or to forward user comments to you about the content that you have posted.  We may also email newsletters, and similar communications about the Service.     
_Opting-Out_.    A user may, at any time, change, correct, modify or delete any personal information they may have provided to HappyNews by sending an e-mail to [info@HappyNews.com](http://www.expertvillage.com/info@ExpertVillage.com). Users can also unsubscribe from any newsletters or opt out of various promotional e-mailings at any time by sending an e-mail to the same address, or by clicking on "unsubscribe" links in each of our newsletters or emails. We reserve the right to send you customary business communications such as acceptance/rejection notices regarding content submissions, general system and administrative messages regarding the Service, address confirmations, and transactional information about your account, and we may not offer you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications so long as you are registered with the Site.   
_Use of Other Information_. We use non-PII about our users for purposes such as measuring the number of visitors to sections of our Site, making the Service more useful to visitors and delivering targeted advertising and non-advertising content.  We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate, non-personally identifiable use.  
_Retention of Information_.  We retain information for as long as required, allowed or we believe it useful, but do not undertake retention obligations.  We may dispose of information in our discretion without notice, subject to applicable law that specifically requires the handling or retention of information.  You must keep your own, separate back-up records.

  3. Does HappyNews Share Information With Other Parties?

We share information with third parties, but only as described in this Section 3.  
_Advertisers and Others_.  We share non-personally identifiable information with advertisers, service providers, and other persons with whom we conduct business. Similarly, these advertisers, service providers, and other persons may share with us non-PII about you that they have independently gathered or acquired.  
_Third Party Services_.  We contract with affiliated and non-affiliated third parties to provide services to us or to you on our behalf. Examples include providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, sending emails to you, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and analyzing data. These third parties may have access to your PII for use solely in connection with these authorized business activities.  
_Business Transfer_.  As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets, or engage in acquisitions, mergers, restructurings, changes of control, or similar transactions.  In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets, and your PII may be subject to such a transfer.  Also, in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, customer information may be transferred to a bankruptcy trustee or debtor in possession and then to a subsequent purchaser.  
_Affiliates_.  We may share PII, non-PII and other information with our corporate affiliates. Some of our most significant affiliates are identified on the website of our parent company, Demand Media, Inc. http://www.demandmedia.com.    
Corporate affiliates are those entities that we control, are controlled by us, or are under common control with us and any joint venture in which any of the controlled entities may participate from time to time. Any use of your information by our corporate affiliates is subject to this Policy or another policy no less protective of your privacy.  Conversely, we may obtain information about you from our corporate affiliates or from your visits to other websites that we or our corporate affiliates control.    
_Compliance and Safety_. We may release user information when we believe release is appropriate to:

  * comply with applicable law, and to respond to legal process, including subpoenas, search warrants and court orders, and to respond to or otherwise address written complaints of copyright infringement;
  * make disclosures under programs intended to prevent potential crimes or investigate persons;
  * enforce or apply agreements, including the Terms; or
  * protect the rights, property, or safety of our Site, our users, or others, including exchanging information with other companies for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

  4. How Secure Is My Information? 

_Your Obligations_.  You must protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Please sign off when finished using a shared computer. Your emails to us are not necessarily secure against interception so do not include sensitive information in them.  We generally will not ask for passwords in an email and you should assume that if you get such a request, it might be fraudulent. YOU MUST DO WHAT YOU REASONABLY CAN TO ENSURE THE SECURITY OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.  
_Our Security Measures_.  We take reasonable precautions to protect the security of our users’ information.  We have physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to help safeguard, prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use your information.  However, neither people nor security systems are foolproof, including encryption systems.  In addition, people can commit intentional crimes, make mistakes or fail to follow policies.  Therefore, while we use reasonable efforts to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.  If applicable law imposes any non-disclaimable duty to protect your PII, you agree that intentional misconduct will be the standards used to measure our compliance with that duty.

  5. What About Links to Other Sites?

The Service contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our Site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects your personally identifiable information. This Policy applies only to information collected by the Service.

  6. What Does HappyNews Do When This Privacy Policy Changes? 

We reserve the right to change our Policy at any time.  Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately.  If we make non-material changes, we will indicate at the top of this page the revised Policy’s new effective date.  If we make material changes, we will notify you by email or through notice on the home page of the Site, and will also indicate so at the top of this page.  The material changes will take effect 30 days after such notice.  We encourage you to refer to this Policy at least every 30 days to check for material changes to this Policy. 

  7. What If I Have Other Questions Or Concerns About Privacy Or This Policy?

_Privacy Concerns_

.  Your use of the Service and any dispute over privacy is subject to the Terms [http://happynews.com/termsofuse.aspx]. If you have any concern about privacy at the Site, please send us a thorough description to [newseditor@happynews.com], and we will try to resolve it. If you think we are in default of the Terms, you may contact us at Our Legal Notices Address below.

 _Identity Theft_

. If you believe that you are a victim of identity theft entitled by law to request information from us, write us at our Legal Notice address below and we will let you know what additional information you must provide to us. After we have received that information, we will supply without charge the information legally required to be disclosed that we then have, subject to applicable law and reserving all of our rights and defenses.

 _Notice Required by Law_

.   In those jurisdictions that permit email notice, if we are required to disclose or provide notice of invasion of certain security systems, we will do so by email to the most current email address provided by you to us. It is critical that you keep your email contact information correct and updated with us at all times. 

_Legal Notices_

.    
For customer service matters (including questions relating to this Policy), you may email us at [newseditor@happynews.com]. To send us a legal notice, mail it by certified mail (return receipt requested) to: HappyNews, Legal Department, 15801 NE 24th St. Bellevue, WA 98008. When we need to contact you, including when we give a legal notice, we may do so to an email address that we have on file for you or we may post notice on the Site. You must keep your email address information accurate. If we make a material change to this Policy, we will notify you by posting notice to the Site for at least 30 days and sending you an email to the email address that we have on record for you.

**You can also contact us at:**   
Customer Care   
HappyNews, Inc.   
1333 Second Street, Suite 100  
Santa Monica, CA 90401   
The trademark Demand Media and all other trademarks listed herein or used in the Service are owned or used under license by Demand Media and its affiliated organizations. The names of third parties and their products mentioned may be their trademarks. You may not use any of the above or other trademarks displayed on the Service or in any Service content. All rights are reserved.

**Copyright © 2008. Demand Media, Inc.**
